This is a work of fiction.
Underage drinking is strongly prohibited and illegal.
Scenes involving alcohol with forceful consumption
and shameful acts are not encouraged.
Please view this as a comedy.
Furthermore, all characters appearing
in this work are of legal age.
It's so hot!
（愛菜(あいな)）あっつーい！
It's a tropical island!
いかにも南国って感じ～
Aina... Everyone's looking at you.
（千紗(ちさ)）愛菜 注目されてる
あ… ご ごめん
でも たぶん…
Oh... Sorry. But I'm probably--
Cheers!
（一同）カンパーイ！
Not as bad as those guys.
あっちよりは
マシなんじゃないかな
We don't know them.
あっちはもう 他人だから
Be passionate, my friends
♪～
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
GRAND BLUE DREAMING
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
An expanding ocean of possibilities
Summer is our amore
We'll swear to the crystal clear sky
Summer is in our hands
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
With a cheerful heart
Don't mess with me
Keep going even if you fall
And let summer take it all
～♪
This is where we're staying for three nights.
（時田(ときた)）ここが
今日から３泊する場所だ
We're staying here?! It's so beautiful!
（愛菜）本当に
こんなきれいなところで!?
（時田）おう
（寿(ことぶき)）食事は自炊だがな
-Yeah.
-We have to cook ourselves, though.
There's even a pool, Kitahara!
（耕平(こうへい)）プールまであるぞ 北原(きたはら)！
What did you say?!
（伊織(いおり)）なんだと！
（時田）ハハハ そう 慌てるな
Don't be in such a hurry!
This work is an original copyrighted material
of the Content Provider. Unauthorized reproduction
or distribution of this work in any form or manner
is prohibited. Some viewers might find this work disturbing
as it may contain strong language, a degree of violence
or adult situations. Viewer discretion is advised.
Please watch it at your own risk.
The story, names, characters and incidents portrayed
in this work are fictitious. No identification with actual
persons, organizations, religions, places and products
is intended. The Content Provider, the producers
and related parties shall have no liability,
as to the accuracy, legality, safety or suitability
for any purpose of the information provided in this work.
The views and opinions expressed herein do not reflect
the views and opinions of the Content Provider,
or any of its affiliates, partners, subsidiaries, or Licensee.
（シャッター音）
（一同）うーん…
It's a tight fit.
かなり 窮屈ですね…
There's four of us sleeping in a room for two.
２人部屋に男４人だからな
It's small. We can't help it.
狭いのはしかたないな
It's partly because you guys are so big.
先輩たちが 体格よすぎるせいでも
あるんですけどね
Well...
こうなったら―
Either me or Kitahara has to sleep on the floor.
俺か北原のどちらかが
床で寝るしかないな
Are you sure?
いいのか？
There's no other way that's physically possible.
物理的に
しかたがないでしょう
Sorry.
すまんなあ…
Anyway, we'll decide later.
とりあえず 決めるのは
あとで考えるとして
Let's go to the beach first!
（一同）何はなくとも
まずは海だ～！
ウフッ ウフフフ…
You look like you're having fun.
（千紗）すごく楽しそうだね
Of course!
そりゃ もちろん！
フッ… 確かにいいよね
You're right. This is nice.
エヘヘ…
Hey! We're going to the beach out back!
（時田）おーい
先に裏の海に行ってるぞ！
Okay!
（千紗･愛菜）はーい！
Sorry to keep you waiting!
お待たせしました～！
-Hey!
-Hurry!
（寿）おお！
（伊織）早く来いよ！
（愛菜）ああ… 幸せ
I'm so happy!
This is a page from my youth!
これが 私の青春の１ページ
An important memory
心のアルバムを飾る
大切な思い出…
in my heart's photo album!
（伊織たちの笑い声）
My album is full of censored images!
（愛菜）私のアルバム
モザイクだらけ！
No need to worry about others
with the place to ourselves.
いやあ 貸し切りは
気兼ねしなくていいな
You're right!
まったくですね
-Let's go somewhere else.
-Why?
移動しましょう
（時田）なぜだ
There's no one here!
We can dress however we want!
ここなら 人がいなくて
自由な格好でいられるだろ
-We're going somewhere else, right?
-Uh... Okay.
移動しますよね
（時田）お… おう
I’m not sure why, but that’s okay.
よく分からんが 了解だ
（にぎわう声）
This spot is nice!
ここならいいですね！
It's just a normal beach.
普通のビーチだな
Well, if you like this spot,
I'm okay with it too.
お前がいいと言うなら
ここでもいいか
This looks fun.
（梓(あずさ)）これはこれで 楽しそうだね
I'll go get some drinks.
（寿）じゃ 飲み物 調達してくる
Oh! Me too!
（愛菜）あっ 私も
（伊織）お？
BEACH EQUIPMENT RENTALS
INQUIRE HERE
They're renting out beach umbrellas.
パラソルのレンタルとかも
あるみたいですね
Let's rent one.
（奈々華(ななか)）借りておきましょうか
I want somewhere to rest.
If you use our service,
（店員）うち 使ってくれたら―
we'll lend you guys an umbrella for free.
パラソル 無料で出しますよ
（耕平･伊織）ん？
Use? What do you mean?
（伊織）使うって何を？
We offer those.
（店員）
ああいうのやってるんですよ
（歓声）
Banana boats?
（耕平）バナナボート？
Why don't you three go ride one?
それなら ３人で
乗ってきたらどうだ？
Uh... I'm fine...
あ いや 俺は…
This is our chance! Let's ride one, Kitahara!
せっかくだし 乗ろうぜ 北原
-I said, I'm--
-So...
だから 俺は…
（耕平）で…
How about deciding where we sleep
using the banana boat?
そいつで 今夜の
寝床を決めるってのはどうだ
-Whoever falls off first, loses.
-What?!
先に振り落とされたほうの負けな
（伊織）はあ？
Of course, if you're too scared, we don't have to.
（耕平）無論 お前が
怖いと言うなら しかたないが
（伊織）んっ…
言ってくれるじゃねえか
You said it first!
Excellent! We're on!
上等！　その勝負 乗ってやる！
Are you sure about this, Iori?
You might end up in the water.
I'm fine!
大丈夫だ　救命胴衣もあるし
作戦もある
They have life vests.
And I have a plan.
A plan?
作戦？
And...
それに いつまでも水を
怖がってなんかいられないからな
I can't stay scared of the water forever!
By the way...
（千紗）ところで これ―
Do people fall off these boats sometimes?
振り落とされることって
あるんですか？
It doesn't happen very often.
あんまりないねえ
-Then we won't be able to decide who wins.
-You're right.
それなら
勝負はつかないかもなあ
だなあ
Well... I guess that's fine.
（耕平）まっ それならそれで
Let's enjoy some marine sports.
（伊織）気持ちよく
マリンスポーツを楽しもうぜ
Okay. Please hold on to the handles tight!
（店員）それじゃ 取っ手に
しっかりつかまってくださいね
（伊織･耕平）ん…
TANNING OIL
You bastard!
（伊織･耕平）貴様～！
You're terrible!
なんて卑劣な野郎なんだ
お前は！
How could you stoop so low?!
お前こそ よくこんな
ゲスなことを思いつくな！
You guys both did the same thing.
（千紗）２人とも
同じことやってんだけど
Here we go!
（店員）行くよ
（エンジン音）
（伊織と耕平の叫び声）
What's wrong, Kohei? You look so tense!
どうした 耕平
顔が引きつってるぜ
I could say the same! Did you pee your pants
because you're scared of the water?
お前こそ 水が怖くて
チビってるんじゃないのか？
Want me to do this with one hand?
なんなら
片手で勝負してやるが？
-Excellent!
-I'm going to accelerate!
上等じゃねえか！
（店員）加速するさー
（伊織･耕平）ふおおおっ！
（千紗）バーカ
Idiots.
（伊織と耕平の叫び声）
That's so nice! They're enjoying their youth!
いいなあ… 青春っぽい
AINA'S VIEW
（伊織･耕平）ハハハ…
（千紗）キャア！
（伊織･耕平）
ふおおおっ！
REALITY
（伊織）ぐっ… いける！
足でふんばれば なんとか
I can do this! If I use my feet, I can make it!
だが それは やつとて同じこと
But he's doing the same thing...
（耕平）ぬうう…
I have to do something about his feet!
（伊織）あの足を
なんとかしなくては！
Over there! It's the voice actress Kaya Mizuki!
向こうに 声優の水樹(みずき)カヤが！
向こうにＡＶ女優が！
Over there! It's a porn actress!
What?!
（伊織･耕平）なにい！
Huh?
（耕平･伊織）あっ…
（海に落ちる音）
-They fell off.
-Oh, dear.
落ちたな
（梓）ありゃまあ
They're so sloppy.
（寿）だらしないやつらだ
（伊織）この ひきょう者！
（耕平）お前がな！
-You coward!
-You're the coward!
-Both of you guys are.
-Hey! Was it fun?
２人ともね
ねえねえ 楽しかった？
I had fun, but...
私は楽しかったけど…
That's so nice! I want to enjoy my youth too.
いいなあ… 私も青春したい
（伊織と愛菜の笑い声）
Then do you want to ride too?
Huh? Are you sure?
いいの？
-We're turning right next.
-Okay.
次 右に曲がるぞ
（寿）おう
It's so stable!
（愛菜）すっごい安定感…
What's wrong, Aina?
どうした？　愛菜
（寿）海水が目に入ったか？
Did you get water in your eyes?
（倒れる音）
（伊織）フゥ…
That was a lot of fun.
遊んだ 遊んだ～
（耕平）疲れた…
I'm so tired.
（梓）ウッフフ まだ初日だよ
It's still the first day.
Hey, you two!
（千紗）２人とも
（耕平･伊織）ぶっ！
The license class starts tomorrow.
明日からは
ライセンス講習だからね
Review the booklets
before you go to bed tonight, okay?
寝る前に 教本の
復習もしておいてね
Okay.
（耕平･伊織）うーっす
By the way, what about your bed, guys?
そういえば
お前らのベッドなんだが
Oh... You're right...
ああ そうでした
Which one of us was winning?
どっちが勝っていましたか？
Kohei won by the height of a wave.
波の差で耕平だったな
（伊織）そんなバカな～！
No way!
A wave?! That's a measurement error!
波の差なんて 誤差だろ！
ん？　どうしたの？
（時田）ああ 実はな…
-What's wrong?
-Well... Actually...
I see. There's not enough beds.
（梓）ああ
ベッドが足りないのか
That's a big problem.
（奈々華）それは困ったわねえ
You guys won't be able to sleep.
そんなんじゃ
ちゃんと眠れないんじゃない？
It'll be dangerous to do the license class
without enough sleep.
寝不足で ライセンス講習は
危ないし…
-Then let's do this!
-Huh?
じゃ こうしましょうか
（千紗･梓）ん？
（波の音）
You can stretch out in this room.
こっちの部屋なら
手足も伸ばせるでしょ？
You have to get a good night's sleep
for the license class.
ライセンス講習のためにも
きちんと寝ないとね
Well then... Good night!
じゃあ おやすみ
Good night!
おやすみなさい
（伊織）うっ うう…
（奈々華と梓の寝息）
（奈々華）うーん…
（伊織）うっ！
（伊織）うおっ！
あっ…
（伊織）ハッ！
（耕平たちの寝息）
（携帯電話の振動音）
CAN'T SLEEP AT ALL
LET ME SLEEP IN YOUR ROOM
ARE YOU ASLEEP?
PLEASE HELP
（耕平）エヘヘヘ…
Good morning!
（千紗･愛菜）おはようございます
-Hey.
-Good morning!
（時田）おう
（寿）おはよう
What's wrong?
どうしたの？
Someone sent me some messages last night.
ゆうべ 寝ているうちに
メッセージが…
Huh?!
（愛菜）んっ！　あ…
What are you doing?!
何やってんだか…
Well... I don't think
まっ あの２人相手に
伊織が何かできるとは思わんが
Iori could do anything to those two.
He might not have gotten enough sleep.
（寿）寝不足になってる
可能性はあるな
Maybe he'll fail the test.
（時田）それで 試験も
さんざんな結果になるとか
I can imagine that.
ありそう…
No. It'll be fine.
いやいや 大丈夫ですよ
It won't make a difference how much he sleeps.
He's always stupid.
やつは 寝不足 関係なく
頭が悪いですから
（一同）ああ…
Why can't any of you guys say something?!
（伊織）誰か 少しは反論しろよ
Hey, Iori.
（時田）おう 伊織
（伊織）おはようございます
Good morning.
I'm telling you now.
（伊織）言っておくが―
I'm confident I can get a higher score than you.
俺は お前より
高得点を取る自信があるぞ？
フン！　バカが よく言うぜ
Idiot! Look who's talking.
ああ？
ドイツ語17点が よく言うぜ
You got 17 points on the German test!
You just got 20 points by chance!
Don't get so cocky!
ケッ たまたまの20点が
偉そうにしてんじゃねえよ
Was 20 a perfect score?
20点満点？
（千紗）100点満点
A perfect score was 100.
I'm starting to feel a little worried.
これは 確かに
心配になってくるな
Do you want to test them?
少し 試してみるか
Hey, you two! I have a question for you.
おーい ２人とも 問題だ
（伊織･耕平）ん？
Which method of moving
long distances is less tiring?
長距離の水面移動は
どっちが疲れない？
A, face-down with your face in the water
Ａ 顔を水につけて
うつ伏せ
or B, face-up?
Ｂ あおむけ
（伊織･耕平）Ｂ
-B!
（正解のチャイム）
（時田）正解
Correct.
How deep can open-water divers dive?
オープンウオーターダイバーが
潜れる最大深度は？
-Eighteen meters!
（伊織･耕平）18メートル
（正解のチャイム）
（寿）常識問題だな
These questions are easy.
I have an easy question to ask too.
あっ じゃあ
私からも常識問題を
Dressing rooms are good--
着替えるときは更衣室を…
（４人）使わない
No!
I haven't finished asking the question!
まだ 問題
言い切ってないんですけど…
Let's try some hard questions.
んじゃ 難しい問題も
いってみるか
At what water temperature
will your hands stop moving?
保温しないと
手が動かなくなる水温は？
えっ それは…
（伊織）18度ですね
Well...
It's 18 degrees.
（正解のチャイム）
（耕平）なっ！
You did it, Iori.
（時田）やるじゃないか 伊織
-You must have studied a lot.
-Impossible!
（寿）よく勉強してるな
バ… バカな！
フッ… 耕平 お前は知るまい
Kohei, you have no idea
how much time I spent
reading that booklet last night.
ゆうべ あの部屋で 俺がどれだけ
教本を読み込んでいたかを
I see.
（時田）なるほどな
（寿）ケガの功名ってやつか
It's what they call a lucky strike.
It's because I studied hard
without letting my eyes stray.
脇目も振らず勉強した成果ですよ
（耕平）クッ おのれ…
You bastard!
At what depth is the safety stop done?
安全停止する深度は？
Three to six meters.
３～６メートル
（正解のチャイム）
-Wow.
-Correct!
おお
（寿）正解だ
Then what is the name of the sharp hook
for cutting fishing line and nets?
じゃあ 釣り糸や網を切る
専用の刃がついたフックは？
A Z knife!
ゼットナイフ
（正解のチャイム）
うんうん
（寿）大したもんだ
Impressive!
What is this hand signal?
このハンドシグナルは？
-Boobs.
-Hey, wait!
“おっぱい”
（時田）おい 待て
What did you say all of a sudden?
突然 何を言ってる？
Uh... I made a mistake.
あ… いや 違った
“こちらを見てください”だ
It's "look this way."
ふむ… なら これは？
-Then what about this?
-Look at the back of my neck.
〝うなじを
見てください 〞
No, that's not it.
いや… そうじゃない
A. CAN'T CLEAR EAR
そっちは見ちゃダメだ
教本に集中しないと
Don't look! I have to focus on the booklet!
The booklet! Focus on the booklet!
教本に… 教本に集中するんだ
（千紗･愛菜）ああ…
I can imagine what was going on
when he read that part.
そのあたりを読んでた状況が
目に浮かぶな
His eyes strayed a lot.
脇目 振りまくりじゃないか
Oh, dear.
（耕平）やれやれ その程度で
集中を乱すとは情けない
I can't believe you weren't able to focus
just because of that.
（千紗･愛菜）あ… わっ！
Huh?!
Good morning.
おはよう
おはようございます
What do you think?
（伊織）どう思う？
I didn't look, Lalako-tan!
見てないよ ららこたん…
So you couldn't sleep all night?
（時田）んじゃ 結局
ひと晩 眠れなかったのか？
Though you don't look very tired.
そのわりには 顔色がいいが
No. I forced myself to sleep.
いえ 無理やり寝ました
（耕平）どうやって？
How?
I made myself black out.
自分で自分を締め落として
That's some skill.
（時田）力業だな
DO NOT ATTEMPT
（耕平）それは
寝たって言えるのか？
Do you call that sleeping?
Well, anyway, I'm glad there were no problems.
まあ なんにせよ
問題なさそうで何よりだ
We'll make breakfast.
朝飯は俺たちで作るから
お前らは復習してるといい
You guys review the material.
-Okay.
（耕平･伊織）ういーっす
We're taking the test here?
（伊織）
ここで筆記をやるんですか？
I thought we'd do it somewhere more formal.
てっきり もっと
お堅い場所でやるのかと…
The test itself is pretty easy.
試験自体は
かなりゆるい感じだぞ
Most of the questions have four choices.
問題は 大体４択だしな
Huh? Really?
え？　そうなんですか？
Then why did we work so hard?
（伊織）なら
俺たちの努力は一体…
What are you talking about?
（時田）何を言う いいか
Listen. This is knowledge about safety.
安全に関する知識だぞ
Studying for safety is never a waste!
いくら勉強しても
損などあるものか
（愛菜）うう…
（耕平）気持ちは分かる
I know how you feel.
You're so different when it comes to diving.
（伊織）ふだんとダイビングで
ギャップがでかすぎるからな
We're starting the test, okay?
試験 始めるよ～
-Do you think they're going to be okay?
-Hmm?
大丈夫かな…
ん？　伊織が心配？
Are you worried about Iori?
Well... He'll be okay.
（時田）まっ 大丈夫だろ
（千紗）でも さっき…
But just now...
Boobs.
“おっぱい”
They're multiple-choice questions.
選択問題だぞ
He doesn't have to write anything.
よけいなことを書く欄などない
If you're worried, why don't you go check?
心配なら 見てきたらどうだ
え？　いや…
Well...
Chii-chan's so cute.
ちーちゃんって
ほんと かわいいねえ
んっ…
BOOBS KITAHARA
（伊織）あう あう あう あう…
あう… 千紗！
Chisa!
What did I do?!
何を！
（紙をそろえる音）
Okay! You all passed!
はい 全員合格です
ハァ…
Why is your face all swollen?
（耕平）なんで お前は
顔が腫れてるんだ？
It's because I stayed up all night.
一夜漬けの弊害だ
Everyone, what's the initial pressure?
（奈々華）
みんな 初期残圧はいくつ？
Two hundred.
200です
-Two hundred.
（愛菜）200です
Let me know when the pressure reaches 60.
残圧が60になったら教えてね
-Okay.
-What happens when it reaches 60?
（愛菜･耕平）はい
60だと何かあるんですか？
That's when we ascend.
（奈々華）
浮上するタイミングなの
PRESSURE ADJUST OF BCD
When you press the
（奈々華）ＢＣＤにある―
power inflator on the BCD,
パワーインフレーターの
ボタンを押すと―
the air enters the vest, and you'll float up.
ベストにエアが入って
浮かびます
When you turn it up and press this button,
上に向けて このボタンを押すと
エアが抜けて 沈みます
the air will go out, and you'll sink.
（伊織）うおお…
THE AIR DIDN'T GO OUT COMPLETELY
（愛菜）うわっ！
うっ… ああっ
COULDN'T RESIST THE WEIGHT OF THE TANK
Take off your regulator,
（奈々華）レギュレーターを
一度外し―
remove the water that got in,
and put it on again.
中に入った水を出して 再装着
（息を吹き込む音）
To remove the water that got in,
（奈々華）中に入った水を
出す方法は―
you can use your breath,
息を吹き込む方法と―
or use the purge button.
パージボタンを使う方法の
２つがあります
Let go of the regulator,
（伊織）レギュを手放し―
and then...
そして再び… うっ！
あわわ…
Calm down.
（奈々華）ゆっくり 落ち着いて
Here's my advice.
千紗の
ワンポイントアドバイス
If you lose your regulator,
レギュを見失った場合は
一度 右肩を下げて―
lower your right shoulder,
and swing your arm up from below.
下から上に大きく腕を回すと
ホースが引っかかります
Your arm will catch the hose.
Great! I'll use the purge button.
（愛菜）よし 私はパージボタンで
（空気が吹き出す音）
（愛菜）あっ
（愛菜）わあっ！
（息を吹き込む音）
Okay.
（奈々華）ＯＫ
We're going to let water into our masks
and get the water out.
（奈々華）マスク内に水を入れ
その水を出します
If you press the top of your mask
and breathe out from your nose,
マスク上部を押さえ
鼻から息を吐くと―
the water will be ejected out the bottom.
水が押し出されて
下から抜けます
Okay.
（奈々華）ＯＫ
（耕平）フッ
I did it!
（愛菜）できた！
（息を吐く音）
（伊織）うっ！　ううっ…
What's your pressure?
（奈々華）残圧は？
Eighty.
（耕平）80です
-Sixty.
（伊織）60です
（愛菜）60です
We're going to ascend.
（奈々華）浮上します
（愛菜･伊織･耕平）ＯＫ
Okay.
The ocean in Okinawa is great!
（寿）やっぱり
沖縄の海は違うなあ
I wish I could stay underwater forever!
（梓）ずっと潜っていたくなるよね
We're also lucky to have such good weather.
天候にも恵まれたしな
（耕平）フン　残圧60どもが
（一同）ん？
Your pressure was only 60.
あん？
俺は最初が180だったんだよ
I started out with only 180!
You said 200 before we started diving!
潜る前 思いっきり
200って言ってたよね？
なんの話？
What’s the commotion?
They're talking about their final pressures.
最終的な残圧の話みたい
Their numbers when they ascended?
（時田）浮上時の数値か
They fight about everything!
（寿）なんでも
争いの種にするな あいつら
（千紗）ハァ…
By the way, how much pressure
did you have left?
ちなみに 先輩たちは
いくつくらいだったんですか？
ん？　110だな
（寿）同じく
-One hundred ten.
-The same for me.
-I had 120.
-One hundred thirty.
120だね
（千紗）130
What about you, Nanaka?
（伊織）奈々華さんは？
I had the same as Chisa-chan.
私も千紗ちゃんと一緒
そ そんなに…
（耕平）桁が違う
-That much?
-It's a difference of a whole decimal!
-You guys could have continued diving.
-Maybe.
（伊織）
じゃ まだ潜れたんですよね？
（時田）かもな
Why didn't you have us ascend first
and continue diving?
俺たちだけ先に上げて―
潜ってたら
よかったんじゃないですか？
ハハハ そうはいかないよ
We can't do that!
Diving is a group activity.
ダイビングは団体行動だからな
If one person ascends, then everyone ascends.
（寿）１人が上がると
みんなで上がるんだ
If we had lots of instructors,
things might have been different, though.
インストラクターが何人もいるなら
話は別だけどね
I see.
なるほど… ってことだ
So that means...
Don't hold us back, you loser!
足を引っ張るなよ
劣等生
You think you're better than me?!
（伊織）だから なんで
上から目線なんだ コラ！
-I am better than you!
-We just said
団体行動って言った直後に
もう輪を乱してるし…
it's a group activity a moment ago,
and they're already fighting.
A group activity...
団体行動…
We can't practice when she's here.
（女子部員）その子いると
全然練習にならないんだよね
She holds us back.
（女子部員）足 引っ張られて
迷惑なんですけど
I'm sorry to ask you this...
（工藤(くどう)）悪いけどさ
遠慮してくれない？
Can you stop coming?
Aina?
（千紗）愛菜？
（愛菜）あっ…
えっ ああ… 何？
What?
You were spacing out. Are you okay?
ぼーっとしてたけど 大丈夫？
What's wrong? Are you tired already?
（伊織）
なんだ もう疲れたのか？
Where's your enthusiasm, Cakey?
（耕平）
気合いが足りんぞ ケバ子
Stop calling me Cakey!
（愛菜）
だから ケバ子って呼ぶな！
I'm not tired, and I'm enthusiastic!
体力も気合いも
全然問題ないから
That's good.
それならいいけど
If you're not feeling well, let us know.
少しでも不調を感じたら
すぐに言ってね
Don't try to push yourself.
せっかくだからなんて
思っちゃダメだよ
It's dangerous to tell lies in the ocean.
海の中のウソは
危険だからね
Understood!
分かりました！
HOW TO EXCHANGE THE OCTOPUS
（奈々華）バディが
エア切れになってしまった場合―
If your buddy runs out of air,
give your octopus,
自分のオクトパス つまり
予備のレギュを相手に渡します
which is a spare regulator, to your buddy.
（梓の呼吸音）
Share your air with your buddy,
（奈々華）自分のエアを
バディに分けつつ―
hold on to your buddy tight, and ascend.
しっかりホールドして
浮上します
（愛菜）うっ うう…
The ocean is so beautiful...
（愛菜）きれいな海…
I can see why they wish they could stay
underwater forever.
みんな ずっと潜っていたいって
思うよね
What's your pressure?
（奈々華）残圧は？
（愛菜）あ…
-Ninety.
-Eighty.
（耕平）90です
（伊織）80です
You guys both still have extra? That means...
（愛菜）２人ともまだ余裕が…
ということは―
We have to stop here because of me...
私のせいで終わり…
I was fine even at 60 just now.
さっきも 残圧60で
まだ余裕あったし―
Maybe I can keep going a little...
少しくらいなら…
ハッ…
ああ…
-Sixty.
-Okay.
（愛菜）60です
（奈々華）ＯＫ
（ボンベを置く音）
ハァ…
Hey, Cakey.
なあ ケバ子
（愛菜）うっ…
-What?
-What do you mean, "What"?
（愛菜）な… 何？
何じゃないだろ
お前 さっき―
You tried to lie about your pressure just now.
残圧ごまかそうとしたろ
（愛菜）うっ…
They just told us it's bad to
海の中でウソはよくないって
言われたばっかりだったのに
tell lies in the ocean.
I know you had the lowest pressure, but still...
いくら 自分が
残圧ビリでもなあ…
But--
だ… だって！
（伊織）ん？
（愛菜）だって…
I didn't want everyone to
私のせいで みんなが早く
上がらなきゃいけなくなると思って
have to ascend just because of me.
え？　残圧勝負で負けたくないから
ウソつこうとしたんじゃないのか？
So you weren't lying just because
you didn't want to lose?
I'd never do that! Uh...
（愛菜）
そんなこと しないわよ！
その… 先輩たちの
迷惑にならないように…
I didn't want to cause trouble for everyone.
（伊織）うーむ…
（愛菜）ん？　どうしたの？
What's wrong?
Nothing. You know,
you're not a good judge of character.
いや なんつーかさ
お前 結構 人を見る目
ないんだなって思ってさ
はあ？　なに？
わけ分かんないんだけど
What?! You don't make sense.
You're the one who doesn't make sense.
わけ分かんないのは
お前だろ？
Do you think they'd care
あの人たちが そんなこと
気にすると思うか？
about something like that?
（愛菜）えっ あっ…
（伊織）すいませーん！
-Excuse me!
-Hey!
（愛菜）ちょっ… ちょっと!?
That's what she said.
（伊織）ってことらしくて
（時田）なるほどな
I see.
You were worried about that?
（寿）んなこと 気にしてたのか
-You know, Aina...
-Yes?
（梓）あのね 愛菜
（愛菜）は はい
Why do you talk so politely to us?
愛菜が私らに敬語を使ってるのは
どうして？
Huh? It's because you're my seniors.
It's natural.
えっ それは
先輩だから当然のことで…
I see. So for you,
うんうん 愛菜にとって―
it's natural to show respect to seniors, right?
先輩に敬意を示すのは
当然のことなんだね
Is that wrong?
それが何か…
In that case...
だったらさあ
（愛菜）ほえっ…
Don't you think it's natural
that your seniors would be forgiving?
尊敬される先輩が寛容なのも
当然だと思わない？
It's no big deal.
You just used up your air a little quick.
いいじゃない 初心者の
エアの消費が早いくらい
Yeah.
まったくだ
That's only natural.
そんなもん 当たり前じゃないか
We'll teach you some tricks.
コツくらい 俺たちが
いくらでも教えてやるぞ
Just work on getting better next time.
んで 次から改善したらいい
（梓）そうそう
Right!
But don't ever lie like that again.
（時田）ただし こういったウソは
二度とつくなよ
Especially when it comes to safety.
（寿）特に 安全に
関することでは絶対にな
Honesty is the best policy.
（梓）人間 正直が一番だからね
Yeah.
（伊織）ってこった
（愛菜）あ…
The seniors here are different, right?
ここの先輩は ひと味違うだろ？
（愛菜）う… うん！
Yeah!
But, you know,
（梓）でも あれだねえ
愛菜が気を使っちゃうのってさあ
if you're worried about what we think,
私らに 身も心も
さらけ出せてないからじゃない？
-it means you haven't opened up to us yet.
-Huh?!
えっ？
（時田）フン！
That makes sense.
一理あるな
It's just a swimsuit!
（梓）水着くらいなら大丈夫！
（愛菜）いや… 無理です
（時田）どれ 手本を見せてやろう
Where?! I'll show you an example!
-This is part of our job too!
-No!
（寿）これも先輩の務めだ！
（愛菜）イヤー！
Everything worked out.
これでよしと…
Iori, it didn't.
伊織君
それが よくもないの
え？　ほかに何か問題が？
Is there another problem?
うーん 今の調子だとね
At this rate,
you're the only one who's going to fail.
伊織君だけ
不合格になっちゃうかも
（波の音）
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
（伊織）マジで？
（奈々華）うん マジで
Seriously.
Here's your mic, Kitahara.
（耕平）ほれ 北原 マイク
Me too? All right, let's do this!
（伊織）俺もかよ
よっしゃ いくぜ！
（寿）おお～ 歌え歌え！
-Yeah, sing your heart out.
-You guys seem to be having fun.
（時田）ノリノリだな
A fairytale whispers
In a fake world
♪～
Hiding in the complete darkness
I reach for the forbidden fruit
In my last days
Now I know the meaning of the song about hope
A broken gear will never stop again
Even if I were to lose everything
I'd still want you to know
Trapped in the sky so far away
I'm praying with ripped off wings
Because we span together
The vows of arpeggio
If life sparkles only to the beat
Of the resonating stars
I'll sacrifice everything
Till death do us apart
Cheers!
～♪
（一同）めんそーれ！
Welcome!
Thanks for going out with me.
（伊織）悪いな
つきあってもらっちまって
No way!
まさか…
I'm getting wet.
（千紗）ぬれちゃう…
Better take off your clothes.
（伊織）服は 脱いだほうが…
（愛菜）ヒッ！
Okay, I will.
（千紗）分かった 脱ぐ
Seriously, what's going on!?
ほんとに
何やってんのー！
NEXT EPISODE
"YOU HAVE THE WRONG IDEA"